这符合她的运动量
THAT WORKS FINE FOR HER.
接着做――25
THERE YOU GO--25.
接下来是“自行车运动”
WE GOT BICYCLES.
我坐下，不多说了。
I'M ON MY BUTT,I'M DONE INSTRUCTING.
我们先向前蹬腿
WE'RE GONNA GO FORWARD FIRST.
我的手放在地上
I'VE GOT MY HANDS ON THE FLOOR.
开始了――1,2,3，
HERE WE GO--ONE, TWO, THREE,
4,5,6,7，
FOUR, FIVE,SIX, SEVEN,
8,9――如果你真心想
EIGHT, NINE--YOU CAN DO THIS--
10――你就能完成
TEN--IF YOU WANT TO.
11, 12, 13,
14, 15, 16--
灼烧感
IT BURNS-- 17, 18,19, 20,
21, 22--
GOING TO 25.
23, 24, 25.
换方向，开始了，
AND REVERSE,HERE WE GO.
不要做错方向
WE'RE NOT GONNA MESS AROUND.
5, 4,
3,2――GO 继续
1，2――我起来
ONE, TWO--I'M UP.
3, 4--
他们来数数，不要停下来。
THEY'RE GONNA COUNT,KEEP MOVING.
漂亮的直线，胸挺直，
NICE STRAIGHT LINE HERE,CHEST IS UP.
转的圈很大。
BIG CIRCLES.
需要的话，双手可以支地
SUPPORT WITH YOUR HANDS IF YOU NEED TO.
詹森，他棒极了，简直是这里的王者。
JASON, HE'S THE KING,HE'S THE RIP KING.
双手高举来保持平衡
HANDS ARE HIGH FOR THE BALANCE,
更多的付出
A LITTLE BIT MORE WORK.
让我骄傲，干的漂亮
MAKES ME HAPPY,NICE.
不错
LOOKING GOOD.
19, 20,
21, 22,
23, 24 AND 25.
开始“蛙展”
TIME FOR CRUNCHY FROG.
大家把手都抬起来
EVERYBODY GETS THEIR HANDS OFF THE FLOOR!
开始了
HERE WE GO.
手臂张开，伸展
ARMS ARE OUT,I WANNA SEE 'EM SPREAD.
5, 4, 3,
2, AND--
内收 张开
WRAP AND OPEN.
2, 3, 4,
5, 6--
这是我们的节奏
HERE'S OUR PACE.
7,8――你如需要休息――
SEVEN, EIGHT--YOU NEED BREAKS--
9, 10--那就休息
9, 10--YOU BETTER TAKE 'EM.
挺胸
12-- GET YOUR CHEST UP.
13--你可以这样做，看到没？
YOU CAN DO THIS,YOU SEE THIS?
调整一下
GATHER YOURSELF.
管他的，我在调整，你也可以
HECK, I'M DOING IT,YOU CAN DO IT, TOO.
准备好了就回到运动中来
THEN YOU JUMP BACK IN WHEN YOU'RE READY.
不分第一部分或者第二部分
THERE AIN'T NO PART ONE AND PART TWO.
这就算第二部分了，最后一个。
IT'S PART TWO, LAST ONE.
我们开始做“盘腿仰卧起坐”
WE GOT CROSS LEG, ALL RIGHT?WIDE LEG SIT-UPS.
有两种方式
SO TWO VERSIONS.
盘腿 或者 伸直腿
CROSS LEG OR WIDE LEG.
伸直腿是简单做法
THIS ONE'S EASIER.
准备好了吗？大家躺下
ARE YOU READY?EVERYBODY BACK.
左手托头，起身转体
LEFT HAND BEHIND THE HEAD, REACH UP AND OVER.
5, 4, 3, 2-- 右手触摸左脚尖
UP, TOUCH YOUR TOE.
如你看到的，开始换手
YOU CAN SEE NOW,SWITCH HANDS.
哦，触摸脚尖，然后躺下
OH, TOUCH THE TOE,COME ON BACK.
起身，注意，要先高举手臂，然后再转体
UP, LOOK, I'M REACHING UP AND THEN OVER.
演示一下错误动作
WHAT I'M NOT DOING IS THIS,
不举手，直接触摸脚尖是错误的。
I'M NOT GOING STRAIGHT AND HERE.
应该高举手，再转体触摸
I'M GOING STRAIGHT UP AND OVER.
很好，接下来，换手
OKAY, AND THEN SWITCH THE HANDS.
高举 然后 转体
UP AND OVER...
UP AND OVER.
注意看，这样做的话，强度更大
NOW, LOOK, THESE ARE A LITTLE BIT HARDER,
因为你不能借助腿部的力量
YOU CAN'T USE THE WEIGHT OF YOUR LEGS.
奥德利亚 向上伸展，然后转体
AUDRA'S GOING UP AND CROSSING OVER.
换另一边
OTHER SIDE.
高举，然后，转体...持续不断
UP AND OVER... ALL DAY LONG.
很好，詹森，漂亮，我的兄弟
GOOD, JASON,NICE, MY BROTHER.
加油，12个了
COME UP.THAT'S 12.
我们还要做一会，一共25个
WE'RE GONNA BE HERE AWHILE.IT'S 25 REPS.
你需要休息，就休息。
YOU NEED A BREAK,TAKE THE BREAK.
很好，现在......
GOOD, NOW...
看看他，看看他，高高伸展然后向下触摸。
LOOK AT HIM, LOOK AT HIM.REACH, WAY UP AND THEN DOWN.
漂亮。注意，他的下巴一直没有触碰到胸
NICE. LOOK, HIS CHIN'S OFF HIS CHEST THE WHOLE TIME,
没有用下巴借力
HE'S NOT TUCKING HIS CHIN IN.
干净利落
GOOD CLEAN FORM.
这是核心动作，不仅是克朗琴动作
THIS IS CORE, THIS IS NOT JUST CRUNCHES, OKAY?
这是重要时刻，这是“腹肌撕裂者”明白？
THIS IS BIG-TIME,"AB RIPPER X," OKAY?
很好
NICE.
我要跟这些孩子们一起完成
I'M GONNA FINISH UP WITH THE KIDS.
开始
HERE WE GO.
向上转体......
AND UP...
我要盘腿做
I'LL EVEN CROSS MY LEGS.
高高伸展，向下触摸
AND UP AND DOWN...
伸展 触摸
再做一个玩玩，高高伸展，向下触摸
ONE MORE FOR FUN,AND REACH UP AND DOWN.
好了，下面是“剪刀腿”
OKAY, TIME FOR FIFER SCISSORS.
两点注意：抬高腿
TWO TIPS:FLEX YOUR FEET
然后尽可能的伸直腿
AND STRAIGHTEN YOUR LEGSTHE BEST YOU CAN.
大家躺下，双手放在体侧
EVERYBODY DOWN, HANDS ON THE FLOOR NEXT TO YOUR BODY.
踢出左腿，离地2.5厘米
KICK THE LEFT LEG OUT,INCH OFF THE FLOOR.
右腿尽可能的抬高
RIGHT LEG UP AS HIGH AS YOU CAN.
像剪刀，明白了？
SCISSOR, GET IT?
听到我喊数才可以换腿
CHANGE WHEN YOU HEARTHE NUMBER ONLY!
5, 4, 3, 2--
1...
2...
3--
没听到数字，不要换腿
DON'T CHANGE WITHOUT THE NUMBER.
4...
5...
6...
7--大家 现在 呼吸
BREATHE PEOPLE, NOW!
8...
9-- 我知道我们做的很慢
I KNOW,WE'RE TAKING OUR TIME.
10-你以为我要喊11了
YOU THINK I'M GONNA SAY 11.
11--
来看看大家做得怎么样
LET'S CHECK ONEVERYBODY.
12-- 很好，奥德利亚
GOOD, AUDRA.
13-- 向她一样的绷直脚尖――14――
KICK THE TOE THAT WAY
脚尖像她一样
FIGHT THE TOE THIS WAY.
15--抬腿
FLEX THE FEET.
16!
换腿
AND SWITCH.
18-- 等待我喊数字
WAIT 'TILYOU HEAR THE NUMBER.
19-- 他正努力地伸直腿
HE'S WORKING TO STRAIGHTEN THAT LEG.
20了，很好
THERE'S 20, GOOD.
21--踢到我的手，很好
HIT MY HAND, GOOD.
22--踢到我的手
HIT MY HAND.
很好
GOOD.
23--这就对了
THAT'S THE GRUNTIN'!
很好，24
GOOD, 24.
就这样，詹森，努力
THAT'S IT,JASON, WORK.
加油，再来一个
COME ON AGAIN,ONE MORE.
看到没，这才是锻炼的样子
SEE, THAT BOY IS WORKING.
这就是我想让你们做的
AND THAT'S WHAT I WANT TO SEE YOU DO.
很好，我们已经做了一半了，
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE HALFWAY ALREADY, MAN,
趴体就要结束了，扫兴啊
PARTY'S ALMOST OVER,WHAT A BUMMER!
好了，你需要休息，尽管休息
ALL RIGHT, IF YOU NEED A BREAK, TAKE 'EM!
我们要做25个
WE'RE DOING 25 A POP.
我们要做“高举”
WE GOT HIP ROCK 'N RAISE.
脚并拢
FEET ARE TOGETHER.
大腿小腿间的距离
THE DISTANCE BETWEEN THE UPPER LEGS AND THE LOWER LEGS
要保持一致。手放这里。
STAYS THE SAME.HANDS ARE HERE.
当我的腿举到一半高度时，脚尖朝向正上方。
WHEN I REACH THE HALFWAY POINT MY TOES GO SKYWARD,
我们姿势要漂亮
LET'S MAKE IT PRETTY.
5, 4,3, 2--
上举，一个
UP, THAT'S ONE...
2...3--不可以比我快
DON'T GET AHEAD OF ME.
4――高高举起 缓缓放下
FOUR-- IT'S UP AND THEN IT'S DOWN.
5――高高举起 缓缓放下
FIVE-- IT'S UP,THEN IT'S DOWN.
6...7--
保持膝盖张开
KEEP THOSE KNEES WIDE.
8......9......
EIGHT... NINE...
10--别这么做（注意错误演示）
DON'T DO THIS.
11-- 看到我的错误演示了吗
YOU SEE WHAT I'M DOING HERE?
12--这样是不对的
THIS IS WRONG.
13--这样的话谁不能做
ANYBODY CAN DO THIS.
14-- 这样才有锻炼效果
THAT'S WHERE THE MONEY IS!
15――高高举起!
15-- GET 'EM UP!
16――这叫做“腹肌撕裂者 X”
16-- IT'S CALLED"AB RIPPER X."
17... 18...
19... 20-- 你需要休息，就休息
YOU NEED THAT BREAK, TAKE IT.
1--还剩四个
YOU GOT FOUR MORE.
2――我知道有灼烧感
TWO-- I KNOW IT BURNS!
23... 24...
25.
正当你觉得这些运动就够好了的时候
JUST WHEN YOU THOUGHT THAT WAS GORGEOUS ENOUGH,
我们要做“跳冲”，或者是“飞天脚”
WE'RE GONNA DO PULSE UP, OR HEELS TO THE HEAVENS--
你想叫它什么都行
WHATEVER YOU WANT TO CALL IT.
现在 抬腿 全抬起来 绷直
NOW LEGS ARE UP,TOGETHER, STRAIGHT.
现在，也许你腿伸不直
NOW, SOME OF YOU CAN'T DO THIS.
你可以稍稍弯曲，但是我要你慢慢努力锻炼
YOU CAN BEND IT, BUT I WANT YOU TO FIGHT OVER TIME
争取能绷直
TO STRAIGHTEN THOSE LEGS.
脚跟朝上 脚尖向下压
HEEL UP, TOES DOWN.
伸直的 而不是冲这个方向
STRAIGHT UP,NOT THIS WAY.
开始
HERE WE GO.
1, 2, 3,
4, 5--我要去看看他们做得怎么样
I'M GONNA CHECK ON THE KIDS.
6--偷看一下
ON MY PEEPS.
7, 8--明白吗，找找偷懒的
NOW YOU GOT ME, JERRY?
9-- 不可以碰到我的手
SHE'S NOT ALLOWED TO HIT MY HANDS.
10__ 到这里
10-- RIGHT IN HERE.
11-- 绷直腿 奥德利亚
STRAIGHTEN THEM,AUDRA.
12-- 努力 挣扎着把屁股抬起来
FIGHT, GET YOUR BUTT IN THE AIR!
13-- 把屁股抬起来
GET YOUR BUTT IN THE AIR!
14-- 这才是我想要的
THAT'S WHAT I WANT.
15-- 这才是一张努力
THAT'S THE FACE OF A GIRL--
16__ 运动的女孩的脸
16-- WHO'S WORKING HARD.
17-- 脚跟冲上
GET THE HEELS IN THE AIR!
18, 19-- 别碰到我的手
DON'T HIT MY HANDS!
20-- 加油 詹森
COME ON, JASON!
21__ 他在挣扎
HE'S FIGHTING.
22-- 他的膝盖有一点弯曲
HIS KNEES ARE A LITTLE BENT.
努力 别碰到我的手
FIGHT, DON'T HIT MY HAND.
23--加油
COME ON.
24 25.
“V字起身”
V-UP/ROLL-UPS.
谁都别先做 我给大家展示一下
NOBODY GO, LET ME SHOWTHE FOLKS THE FORM.
手永远不要越过你的头
YOUR HANDS NEVER GO OVER YOUR HEAD.
必须指向天棚
HANDS TO THE CEILING ONLY.
这是一个动作 躺回去
THAT IS NUMBER ONE,WE ROLL BACK.
当后背触地 双腿抬起
WHEN MY LOWER BACK HITS THE FLOOR THE LEGS COME UP
然后我起身
AND THEN I COME UP ONTO MY BUTT.
这是第2个
明白了吗 我们要做25个
YOU GOT IT?WE'RE GONNA DO 25 TOTAL.
将后背挺起 离开地板
GET YOUR LOWER BACK OFF THE FLOOR.
如果你只能做到这样......
IF YOU CAN ONLY DO THIS IN THE PULSE-UP...
我不在乎 但是保证准时起身
I DON'T CARE,BUT IN TIME GET IT UP.
我说完了
I'M DONE CHATTING.
5, 4,
3, 2, 1--
摸脚尖
TOUCH THEM TOES.
起来 下去
GET IT UP AND COME DOWN.
第三个
THAT'S THREE...
第四个
THAT'S FOUR...
第五个――明白了吗
THAT'S FIVE--YOU GOT IT?
第六个――我们动作要一致
THAT'S SIX--LET'S GET SYNCHRONIZED.
屈体起身
ROLL IT UP.
7--躺下去
COME ON DOWN.
起身
PULSE IT UP.
8...
第九个了
THAT WOULD BE NINE...
10...
想象你要做一百个
IMAGINE YOU GOTTA DO A HUNDRED OF 'EM!
11-- 25个也不算很糟糕了
11-- 25 DOESN'TSOUND SO BAD.
很好。12......
GOOD.12...
13...
让我看看他们
LET ME SEE 'EM.
很好 奥德利亚 加油
GOOD, AUDRA,COME ON.
屈体起身
ROLL IT UP!
手不能超过这 她起身了
THE HANDS NEVER COME PAST HERE, SHE PULSES UP.
屈体起身
ROLL IT UP!
詹森 手不能超过这里 起来
JASON, HANDS NEVER COME PAST HERE, GET IT UP.
加油 哥们 起来
COME ON, DUDE.ROLL IT UP!
后背离开地板
GET THAT LOWER BACK OFF THE FLOOR AND GET UP!
就这样 加油
THERE IT IS, COME ON.
做得好 就这么锻炼
NICE WORK, THAT'S THE WAY TO FIGHT.
来看看亚当
LET'S CHECK OUT ADAM.
很好
NICE.
起来
ROLL IT UP.
好 24了 让我看看第25个
GOOD, THAT'S 24,LET ME SEE 25.
你完成了 干得好 哥们
AND YOU ARE DONE,NICE WORK, MY MAN.
他要多做 真是勇猛
AND A BONUS,HE'S A MADMAN.
好了 “侧体V字屈体”
OKAY, OBLIQUE V-UPS.
大家右侧躺下 开始了
EVERYBODY ON YOUR RIGHT SIDE, HERE WE GO.
规则是这样 屈腿30度
SO HERE'S THE DEAL,30-DEGREE ANGLE.
右手放右侧 左手放脑后
RIGHT ARM, RIGHT SIDE,HAND BEHIND THE HEAD.
用臀部的力量屈体
LET'S GET UP ON YOUR HIP AND BUTT.
腿保持伸直
KEEP YOUR LEGS STRAIGHT.
开始后 让肩膀和
ONCE YOU START, KEEP YOUR SHOULDER
脚离开地板
AND YOUR FEET OFF THE FLOOR.
5, 4,
3, 2--
1, 2, 3,
4, 5,
6, 7,
8, 9,
10, 11--
坚持住
HANG IN THERE.
需要就休息
12-- NEED A BREAK,TAKE IT.
13, 14--抬起来
GET IT UP!
15--加油 还有十个
COME ON,10 MORE.
1, 2, 3,
4, 5--像机器一样
BE A MACHINE.
6―― 加油
SIX-- COME ON!
7, 8,
9--
最后一个 棒极了
LAST ONE,GORGEOUS.
另一边 转过去
OTHER SIDE,FLIP IT AROUND.
:)
他们很努力 我知道你也是
THEY'RE WORKING HARD,I KNOW YOU ARE!
继续
HERE WE GO.
左边 左手
LEFT SIDE, LEFT HAND.
30度
30-DEGREE ANGLE.
手放脑后 说完了
HAND BEHIND THE HEAD.I'M DONE CHATTING.
5,4,
3,2--
1,2,3,
4――如果你能
FOUR-- KEEP THOSE LEGS STRAIGHT.
5――腿要伸直
IF YOU CAN.
6,7,
8,9--
腿并拢
LEGS TOGETHER.
10――来看看他们
10-- LET'S SEE 'EM.
11, 12, 13--
腿抬起来 奥德利亚 加油
GET THOSE LEGS UP, AUDRA.14-- COME ON!
15-- 很努力
WORKING HARD.
16-- 詹森 我要到你这来了
JASON,I'M COMING TO YOU.
起来 ...... 起来
GET UP...GET UP.
接触到了
MAKING CONTACT!
这家伙膝肘接触到了 干得漂亮
THE MAN'S MAKING CONTACT,ELBOW-THIGH, NICE WORK.
23, 24, 25.
“腹肌...撕裂...者...X”
"AB... RIPPER... X."
我们来“攀腿”
LET'S CLIMB OUR LEGS.
展示三个版本给你
THREE VERSIONS I'M GONNA SHOW YA.
如果要爬右腿
IF I'M CLIMBING MY RIGHT LEG
左脚跟愈靠近我屁股
THE CLOSER MY HEEL IS TO MY BUTT
就越难
THE HARDER IT IS.
困难 简单 最简单
HARDER, EASIER,EASIEST.
明白了
YOU GOT IT?
开始爬吧 每侧12次
LET'S CLIMB,12 PER SIDE.
5, 4,
3, 5, 1--
我起来 触摸脚尖
AND I'M UP,AND I TOUCH MY TOE.
AND I'M UP, AND I TOUCH MY TOE.
我起来了
AND I'M UP--
现在亚当做的是“直腿版”
NOW ADAM'S DOING STRAIGHT BOTTOM LEG.
他在做简单版的 更容易些
HE'S DOING THE EASY VERSION, EASIER.
詹森两分两次爬 1 2
JASON'S GOT TWO-HAND GRAB,ONE, TWO.
奥德利亚 她直接起身
AND AUDRA, SHE'S JUST GOING STRAIGHT UP.
看到区别了吗
YOU SEE THE DIFFERENCE?
这样更难......这样更难
THAT IS HARDER...THAT IS HARDER.
或者你可以从内膝盖处抓一次
OR YOU START ON THE INSIDE AND REACH UP AND DO ONE GRAB.
你可以抓四次
YOU CAN DO FOUR GRABS.
我不管 只要碰到腿就行
I DON'T CARE, JUST GET UP YOUR LEG.
抓的次数越少 就越难
THE LESS GRABS THE HARDER IT IS.
很好 再来一次
GOOD, ONE MORE TIME.
换 ...... 另一边
SWITCH...OTHER SIDE.
5, 4,
3, 2, 1--
这是一个 躺下去
THAT'D BE ONE, COME ON DOWN.
退绷直 保持稳定
KEEP THE LEG STRAIGHT,KEEP IT ON ONE PLANE,
别乱晃
DON'T LET IT MOVE AROUND.
这是个不抓的
HERE'S A NO-GRAB.
4--起来
REACHING UP.
不抓 只触摸
NO GRAB, JUST TOUCHING.
这是抓两次的 就这样
HERE'S A TWO-GRAB,THERE YOU GO.
在膝盖和脚趾处抓两下
TWO-GRAB AT THE KNEEAND THE TOE.
怎样有趣怎么做
MAKE IT INTERESTING FOR YOURSELF.
感觉怎么样
HOW DO YA FEEL THAT DAY?
用尽全力
DO WHAT YA CAN.
越少抓腿 就越难
THE LESS GRABS THE HARDER IT IS.
脚后跟越内收 就越难
THE FURTHER THIS HEEL IS IN, THE HARDER IT IS.
很好 再来一次
NICE, ONE MORE TIME.
然后...... 起来
AND... COME ON UP.
哦 干得很漂亮
OH, VERY NICE.
我们就要强势结尾了
NOW WE'RE GONNA FINISH UP STRONG.
我不敢相信就快结束了 让我很难过
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT'S ALMOST OVER, MAKES ME SAD.
梅森转体
MASON TWIST!
用拳头 双手交叉 握拳
BRING THE FIST, THE HANDS TOGETHER, CLASP THE HANDS.
你每次都需要和地板接触到
YOU'RE GONNA MAKE CONTACT WITH THE FLOOR EVERY TIME.
腿抬起来 从右边开始
GET THE LEGS UP, WE'RE GONNA START WITH THE RIGHT FIRST.
40次
40 TIMES.
做越多越好 我们要做40个
DO AS MANY AS YOU CAN, WE'RE DOING 40.
兴许还要多做几个
WE MIGHT EVEN DO SOME EXTRA.
开始吧 5,4,3,2――
COME ON UP, FIVE, FOUR,THREE, TWO AND--
1,2,3,4,――像划独木舟一样
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR-- WE'RE GOING KAYAKING.
5,6,7,8__
9--还有十个
10 TO GO!
1,2,3,4――
5,6,7,8,――
9, 20,加油
COME ON NOW!
1,2,――转
ONE, TWO-- TURN.
3,4,5,6――
7――加油 奥德利亚
SEVEN-- COME ON, AUDRA.
8,9,――
30, 31, 32,
33, 34, 35--加油！
COME ON!
36, 37, 38, 39--多做 加油
BONUS, COME ON!
一个，两个，三个――
6-- 4, 5,坚持
HANG IN.
7--坚持
8,9――
10.
嗯
感觉很好
I FELT THAT.
你做完“腹肌撕裂者X”了 男男女女们
YOU'VE JUST COMPLETED"AB RIPPER X," BOYS AND GIRLS.
如果你和我们一样都坚持了下来 你做了
IF YOU STUCK WITH US, YOU DID 349
349个黄金核心腹肌训练
CORE/AB EXERCISES.
非常感谢
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
大家伙放松一下
LET'S DO A LITTLE STRETCH EVERYBODY.
我们做一下“上犬式”
LET'S DO A LITTLE UPWARD DOG.
保护一下胃部 来吧 开始
LET'S TAKE CARE OF OUR STOMACH. COME ON, HERE WE GO.
趴在你的瑜伽垫上
GET ON YOUR MATS.
你想做“眼镜蛇式”效果也是一样的
YOU CAN DO COBRA, TOO,HERE, IF YOU WANT.
就这样
THAT'S IT.
上犬式腹部、腿最好离开地面（力量弱的学员,部分大腿以及小腿也可以不离地,但是要求大腿前部提起）,脚趾背面着力,大腿内旋,臀部收缩并将耻骨向肚脐方向用力,尾骨向耻骨方向压.
UPWARD DOG,KNEES ON.
眼镜蛇式下腹部、骨盆、大腿、小腿都落在地上,脚趾不着力,脚背落地,大腿内侧肌肉向下旋转
COBRA, KNEES DOWN.
记住这句话
REMEMBER,TIP OF THE DAY:
不要每天做 不需要
DON'T DO THIS EVERY DAY,YOU DON'T NEED IT.
你不每天锻炼别的部位
YOU DON'T WORK OTHER PARTS OF YOUR BODY EVERY DAY,
腹肌也不应该每天锻炼
AND YOU SHOULDN'T WORK ABS EVERY DAY,
尤其是“腹肌撕裂者X”
ESPECIALLY"AB RIPPER X."
来做一下“婴儿式”
LET'S ALL GO INTO CHILD'S POSE.
译者注：新手应适当延长放松瑜伽时间，注意腿部的抻拉。
他们要保持动作，我要说:
THEY'RE GONNA STAY THERE AND I'M GONNA SAY...
干的漂亮
NICE WORK.
若果这是你当天最后一个健身运动
IF THAT'S YOUR LAST WORKOUT OF THE DAY
没有比现在更适合喝“恢复饮料”的时候了（蛋白质冲剂）
IT'S A GOOD TIME FOR YOUR RECOVERY DRINK.
我高度推荐
I HIGHLY RECOMMEND IT.
若反映良好，将着手翻译全部P90X训练字幕，作者信息等若被私自修改，或被私自用于商业用途，将即刻删除字幕，并停止之前11部P90X训练的翻译。
一人翻译势单力薄，您若愿意参与翻译，我已做好时间轴和英文字幕，请联系lyz625@msn.com索要，让我们一起打败淘宝盗版字幕的垄断。